Guide to the JDub Records Archive 2001-2011 MSS.330
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Original Media
  - Subseries A: Media
    - Strom, Yale - "Dveykes / Adhesion", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0340)
    - The Sway Machinery, 2006 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0341)
    - The Sway Machinery - "Hidden Melodies Revealed" unmastered, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0342)
    - The Sway Machinery - "Klezmer Collection", 2002 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0343)
    - The Sway Machinery - "Live at Center Stage" Atlanta Jewish Music Fest., 2011 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0344)
    - Tafilalt Trio, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0345)
    - Talat - Sampler, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0346)
    - Talat - "Unwrapped", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0347)
    - Tali Elias - "For Loving Me", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0348)
    - Tali Elias - "We've Got it All Wrong" with Gilad Shalit, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0349)
    - Third World Love - Rough Mixes, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0352)
    - Tin Hat Trio, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0353)
    - Tiny Animals - "Sweet Sweetness", 2009 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0354)
    - Todd Kessler and Boomerang, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0355)
    - Tri-Pinnacle - "Diagnol Ryme Garganchula", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0356)
    - Tzofia, Divahn-Ayni - Initial Mix, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0357)
    - Undzer Velt, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0358)
    - Unity Sessions at Celebrate Brooklyn, 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0359)
    - The Upwelling, 2006 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0360)
    - Useless Action, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0361)
    - Useless Beauty, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0362)
    - Vagabond Opera, 2009 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0363)
    - Varsouviana, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0364)
    - Villarreal, Yosef Daniel, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0365)
    - The Wailing Wall, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0366)
    - The Wailing Wall, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0367)
    - The Wailing Wall - revised, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0368)
    - The Wailing Wall - Unmastered, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0369)
    - Wellsprings - "Simcha Kanter", Undated (Box 32, Disk ID; 330.0370)
    - Weinstock, Mark, 2004 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0371)
    - Weizman, Ran, Undated (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0372)
    - White Shabbos - "Al Tirah", 2005 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0373)
    - Yad - "Compilation", 2003 (Box 32, Disk ID: 330.0374)
    - Yasmine Ariel - "One First Time", Unated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0375)
    - Yasmine Ariel - "One First Time" single, 2009 (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0376)
    - Yedi, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0377)
    - Yizkor - With David Chevan, Cantor Martin Levson, and the Afro-Semitic Experience, 2007 (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0378)
    - Yosef, Tomer, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0379)
    - Yosef, Tomer - Instrumentals, audio, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0380)
    - Yosef, Tomer - Instrumentals, Wav, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0381)
    - Yosef, Tomer - "Laughing Underground" v.2, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0382)
    - Yvangelynn, 2007 (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0383)
    - Zagnut Cirkus Orkestar - rough mixes, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0384)
    - Zohar - "Have You Got Any Faith?", Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0385)
    - Unmarked CD, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0386)
    - Unmarked CD, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0394)
    - [Ayn Deber Kazeh Yeled R'e] (There is no Such Thing as a Bad Child) In Hebrew, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0387)
    - [Berven Y'Hed Kevkeby Bevqer] (Baron and the Morning Stars) In Hebrew, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0388)
    - [Heml'hemvet Beyneynev] (Our Wars) In Hebrew, Undated (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0389)
    - JDub Sampler, 2006 (Box Shared Fales 058, Disk ID: 330.0390)
      Format: Pocket CD
    - So Called - "Rock the Belz", 2009 (Box 29, Cassette ID: 330.0391)
      Format: BetaCam
    - So Called - "You Are Never Alone", 2007 (Box 29, Cassette ID: 330.0392)
    - So Called - "You Are Never Alone" Closed Captioned, 2007 (Box 29, Cassette ID: 330.0393)
    - The 8 - DC, Version 1, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0395)
    - The 8 - LA (Extra), Version 2, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0396)
    - The 8 - Loop, welcome, blessings, Harold & Kumar, Version 1, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0397)
    - The 8 - Loop, welcome, blessings, Harold & Kumar, Version 1, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0398)
    - The 8 - Loop, welcome, blessings, Harold & Kumar, Version 2, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0399)
    - The 8 - Loop, welcome, blessings, Harold & Kumar, Version 2, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0400)
    - The 8 - Q Times, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0401)
    - The 8 - Seattle, Version 1, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0402)
    - The 8 - Seattle, Version 1, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0403)
    - Amitai, Paul - "Installations and Performance", 2004 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0404)
    - Amitai, Paul - "Installations and Performance", 2004 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0405)
    - Andra La Moussia, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0406)
    - Ariel, Yasmine - Performance Video Clips, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0407)
    - Axum - Ahla Combina Video, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0408)
    - Axum - Ma Im Hakesef video, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0409)
    - Axum - Ma Im Hakesef video, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0410)
    - Balkan Beat Box, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0411)
    - Balkan Beat Box - B. Chicks, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0412)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Bulgarian Chicks Single Files, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0413)
    - Balkan Beat Box - DVD, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0414)
    - Balkan Beat Box - DVD, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0415)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Hermetico Live, NTSC version, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0416)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Hermetico Live, NTSC version, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0417)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Hermetico Live, NTSC version, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0418)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Hermetico Live, PAL version, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0419)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Hermetico Live, PAL version, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0420)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Jewltide Brooklyn, 2005 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0421)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Kind og Home" film and "Hermetico" DVD, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0422)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Knit LA, 2005 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0423)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Live Show, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0424)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Louisiana, 2007 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0425)
    - Bons Baisers de France, 2007 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0426)
    - Dub LFO, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0427)
    - Exodus - Slam Demo, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0428)
    - Golem - DVD Demo, 2005 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0429)
    - Golem - Fox Morning News, 2007 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0430)
    - Golem - at Knit, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0431)
    - JDub - JCF LA, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0432)
    - JDub - Play start, RYKO, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0433)
    - JDub Records, DeLeon, LaSerena - Music video, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0434)
    - Jewcy - "2 Minute Mitzvah", Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0533)
    - Jewcy - "What Matters Now", Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0534)
    - Judisch[e] Hip Hop, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0435)
    - Levanon, Gil, 2006 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0436)
    - Lockwood, Jeremiah - "Letterbox", Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0437)
    - Matisyahu - On Current TV, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0438)
    - Matisyahu - JDub TV clips, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0439)
    - Matisyahu - "King Without a Crown" first rough cut, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0440)
    - Matisyahu - Live in Paris, 2004 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0441)
    - Matisyahu - PR DVD, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0442)
    - Matisyahu - Recent National Television Appearances, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0443)
    - Matisyahu - "Youth", Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0444)
    - Oy Division! - "Live at Tel-Aviv", Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0445)
    - The Smoking Cat, a Film by Ellie Brickman, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0446)
    - So Called - 500 Pound Planet, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0447)
    - So Called - Full Quality, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0448)
    - So Called - Plus sur Commando", 2007 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0449)
    - So Called - Rock Belz, 2009 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0450)
    - So Called - "You Are Never Alone", Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0451)
    - Sway Machinery - "Weeds", Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0452)
    - Tablet Magazine - The Situation Room, CNN, 2009 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0453)
    - There is no Bad Boy, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0454)
    - Vodka Latka / Festival of Rights, 2006 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0455)
    - Unity 1, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0456)
    - Unity 2, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0457)
    - Unity 3, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0458)
    - Unity Sessions, 2004 (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0459)
    - Unity Sessions, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0460)
    - Zachor, A Memorial for Marla and Ben, disk 1, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0461)
    - Zachor, A Memorial for Ben and Marla, disk 2, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0462)
    - Unmarked DVD, Undated (Box 19, Disk ID: 330.0463)
    - Golem Demo, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0464)
      Format: Audiocassette
    - Golem Demo, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0465)
    - Pearl Bubblegum Babylonia, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0466)
    - Amst / Berlin, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0467)
      Format: Mini DV
    - Amst / London, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0468)
    - Ben - Perf. Skirball JDub, 2003 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0469)
    - Ben at Tonic, 2003 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0470)
    - Berlin / Paris, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0471)
    - Concert May 28 - shot Ronit Avni, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0472)
    - DeLeon, 2008 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0473)
    - DeLeon at City Winery, 2009 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0474)
    - Gangsta Rabbi, 2010 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0475)
    - Gangsta Rabbi #2, 2010 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0476)
    - Girls in Trouble - Promo Video, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0477)
    - Golem at Knit, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0478)
    - Halloween, 2002 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0479)
    - HaMaabada - Israel, 2005 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0480)
    - Harold and Kumar, 2007 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0481)
    - Israel, 2005 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0482)
    - JDub INTVS tape 1, 2004 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0483)
    - JDub INTVS tape 2, 2004 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0484)
    - JDub Purim, 2003 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0485)
    - JDub Video (new), 2004 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0486)
    - Jewcy - Right Camera, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0487)
    - Jewltide - BBB Brooklyn, 2005 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0488)
    - London interview inc. Sunday Times, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0489)
    - Matis[yahu] at Knit Comedy Night, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0490)
    - Matis[yahu] at Southpaw, tape #2, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0491)
    - Matis[yahu] at Southpaw, tape #3, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0492)
    - Showalter show 1, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0493)
    - Showalter show 1, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0494)
    - Showalter show 2, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0495)
    - Showalter show 2, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0496)
    - Showalter show 2, short tape, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0497)
    - Showalter show 3, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0498)
    - Showalter show 3, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0499)
    - Showalter show 3 and crowd, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0500)
    - Showalter show 4, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0501)
    - Showalter, Wail, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0502)
    - Soulico, 2007 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0503)
    - Sway HMR 9/8/10, 2010 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0504)
    - Sway HMR 9/8/10, 2010 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0505)
    - Tahli JDub tape, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0506)
    - Treasurer's Report, 2003 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0507)
    - Vodka Latke 12/05, 2005 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0508)
    - Vodka Latke SF 12/22/05, 2005 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0509)
    - Yom Yerushalaim Concert, 2003 (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0510)
    - Unmarked cassette, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0511)
    - Unmarked cassette, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0512)
    - Unmarked cassette, Undated (Box 30, Cassette ID: 330.0513)
    - ARD German Television, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0514)
      Format: VHS
    - JDub Promo, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0515)
    - JDub Records, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0516)
    - Matisyahu - CNN Headline News interview Tue. 6/29, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0517)
    - Matisyahu - "Faith in America" on MSNBC, Mar. 25, 2005 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0518)
    - Matisyahu - Hasidic Reggae Superstar - Booking and Info., Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0519)
    - Matisyahu - Hasidic Reggae Artist, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0520)
    - Matisyahu - "Jimmy Kimmel Live, 4.18.05" copy 1, 2005 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0521)
    - Matisyahu - "Jimmy Kimmel Live, 4.18.05" copy 2, 2005 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0522)
    - Matisyahu - Lisa Bloch Matt Miller Film 8/7/02 - Rough cut, 2002 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0523)
    - Matisyahu - "MTV Backstage Pass" 5/18/05, 2005 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0524)
    - Matisyahu - Sample footage 7-7-03, 2003 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0525)
    - Matisyahu - Shore Fire Media, 2005 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0526)
    - Matisyahu - Shore Fire Media, "Matisyahu, Musical Artist", 2005 (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0527)
    - So Called at JDub's Slivovitz & Soul Party, Undate (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0528)
    - Steve Harvey's Big Time Challenge - show # 208, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0529)
    - Tahli - Concert, raw footage..., Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0530)
    - Unity Sessions - Prospect Park, Brooklyn, clips, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0531)
    - WB11, Undated (Box 20, Cassette ID: 330.0532)
  - Subseries B: Papers removed from media
    - JDub Footage list, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0000b)
    - Amitai, Sharron Topper, 2010 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0010b)
    - Applebaum, Talia - "Flashes in the Darkness", 2006 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0012b)
    - Betzalel, Einat, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0038b)
    - Conjoin - "Long Live the King", Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0058b)
    - Dreiblatt, Ian, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0076b)
    - Duchampion, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0079b)
    - Eilat, Yoni, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0084b)
    - Electric Simcha, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0085b)
    - Folklezmer, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0095b)
    - Fox-Rosen, Benjy, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0097b)
    - Funk's, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0103b)
    - Great Tap Root, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0120b)
    - Hanukkah Roughs, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0122b)
    - The Hoodska Explosive - "The Misleading", Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0133b)
    - Incus, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0135b)
    - Lazarus, Ariel, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0161b)
    - Mad Happy, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0170b)
    - Made Men - Mixtape, 2007 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0171b)
    - Manach, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0172b)
    - Maroko, Jordan, 2008 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0175b)
    - Matisyahu - set lists, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0179b)
    - Midnight Peacocks, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0217b)
    - My Silent Bravery, 2010 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0226b)
    - My Yiddish Mambo, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0227b)
    - Nayo, Gilmo, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0229b)
    - Radioyaakov, 2007 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0253b)
    - Reuven, Ben, 2010 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0262b)
    - Rothman, Chana, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0274b)
    - Sandcastle, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0279b)
    - Sasson, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0281b)
    - Scatalogics, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0284b)
    - Serper, Leonora, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0287b)
    - Sharvit, Tomer, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0291b)
    - Shmuel, Rav, 2004 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0293b)
    - Shtetlblasters, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0301b)
    - Tali Elias, 2011 (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0348b)
    - Tiny Animals, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0354b)
    - Useless Action, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0361b)
    - Varsouviana, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0364b)
    - Yedi, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0377b)
    - Yosef, Tomer - "Laughing Underground", Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0382b)
    - Yasmine Ariel, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0407b)
    - Pearl Bubblegum Babylonia, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 330.0466b)
- Series VII: Objects
  This series contians objects kept by JDub Records, mostly promotional material for events and T-shirts.
  - Buttons - "Ask me about JDub Records", Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0001)
  - Buttons - JDub tablet logo, Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0002)
  - Buttons - The Wailing Wall, Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0003)
  - Extra Gobos, NYC, Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0039)
  - Guitar pick - "Joyous Holidays, Mark Schwartz and Valerie Marcus", Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0004)
  - Hannukah candles - JDub / The 8 (3 boxes), 2007 (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0005)
  - JDub NY wrist-band, Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0006)
  - Jewcy baseball cap, Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0007)
  - Jewish Music Awards - SoCalled - Best New Album certificate, 2006 (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0008)
  - Keycard - Tablet magazine, Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0009)
  - Matisyahu 7" Single cardboard stand, Undated (Box 7, Object ID: 330.2.0038)
  - T-Shirt - Balkan Beat Box - green, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0010)
  - T-Shirt - Balkan Beat Box - red, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0011)
  - T-Shirt - Balkan Beat Box - blue, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0012)
  - T-Shirt - Golem - grey, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0013)
  - T-Shirt - Golem - blue/grey, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0014)
  - T-Shirt - Golem - brown, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0015)
  - T-Shirt - JDub - brown, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0016)
  - T-Shirt - JDub - red, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0017)
  - T-Shirt - JDub - green, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0018)
  - T-Shirt - JDub 5th Anniversary - brown, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0019)
  - T-Shirt - JDub, The 8 - black, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0020)
  - T-Shirt - JDub boombox design - red, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0021)
  - T-Shirt - JDub - boombox design - green, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0022)
  - T-Shirt - JDub flower design - white, Undated (Box 8, Object ID: 330.2.0023)
  - T-Shirt - JDub NY - blue, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0024)
  - T-Shirt - JDub tablet logo - blue, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0025)
  - T-Shirt - JDub tablet logo - light blue, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0026)
  - T-Shirt - JDub tablet logo - yellow, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0027)
  - T-Shirt - Jewcy - blue / white, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0028)
  - T-Shirt - Jewcy - blue, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0029)
  - T-Shirt - Jewcy - pink, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0030)
  - T-Shirt - Jewcy dancing figures - grey, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0031)
  - T-Shirt - Jewcy samech logo - white, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0032)
  - T-Shirt - Jewcy samech logo - black, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0033)
  - T-Shirt - Jewcy skull - black, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0034)
  - T-Shirt - Michael Showalter cat hat - white, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0035)
  - T-Shirt - Soulico - white, Undated (Box 9, Object ID: 330.2.0036)
  - Birthright Israel / JDub - The 8 banner, Undated (Box 10, Object ID: 330.2.0037)
- Series VIII: Data Storage
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  This series contains digital photographs and data from JDub events, artists, and productions.
  - The 8: A Crazy Worldwide Hannuka Party - photobooth, Seattle WA, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0001)
  - The 8 - Large files and websize files, photos, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0002)
  - The 8 - Logo still, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0003)
  - The 8 - NYC photobooth, Webster, disk 1, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0004)
  - The 8 - NYC photobooth, Webster, disk, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0005)
  - The 8 - Photobooth pics, Boston, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0006)
  - The 8 - Photobooth pics, LA, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0007)
  - The 8 - Reproduction photos, Black and White Jacksons, and Misc. pics, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0008)
  - The 8 - S.F. pics, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0009)
  - The 8 - Webster Hall, Dec. 8, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0010)
  - American Shmidol - Greg Wilson, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0011)
  - American Shmidol - Jori Klein, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0012)
  - Balkan Beat Box - El Rey 9/9/08, 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0013)
  - Balkan Beat Box - Kushner photos, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0014)
  - Balkan Beat Box - Seth Kushner pics, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0015)
  - Balkan Beat Box - Video edits by Alex Rowe, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0016)
  - DeLeon - JDub concert, Washington DC, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0017)
  - DeLeon and Sway Machinery - At Grog Shop, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0018)
  - DeLeon and Sway Machinery - at Troubadour 12/20/08 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0019)
  - Golem - At DBA, Nov. 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0020)
  - Golem - At DBA II, Nov. 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0021)
  - Golem - NOVA Project files, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0022)
  - Golem - Pictures, alternate apparel photo shoot, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0023)
  - Heeb - JDub - SXSW - Sasquatch, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0024)
  - Hidden Melodies Revealed - Photos, 2009 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0025)
  - Israel Concert Pictures, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0026)
  - JDub - 5th Anniversary Concert, July 20, 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0027)
  - JDub - Birthright Israel, 12/8/07, 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0028)
  - JDub - Denver, CO, 7/2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0029)
  - JDub - HMR LA '09, 2009 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0030)
  - JDub - Labor Day BBQ, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0031)
  - JDub - Party, Seattle WA, Dec. 8, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0032)
  - JDub - Photobooth S.F., 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0033)
  - Jewcy, 2006 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0034)
  - Jewcy - Chanukah Crobar, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0035)
  - Jewcy - Christmas Party (4 corners), 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0036)
  - Jewcy - Jeffrey Goldberg, rough cut, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0037)
  - Jewcy Site Design - Point Five Design, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0038)
  - Jewltide - North Star Bar, Philly, 12/27/08, 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0039)
  - Jewltide - Shuli 12/24/06, 2006 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0040)
  - The LeeVees - 8 Concert, Washington DC 12/8/07, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0041)
  - LINO - 2500 4x6" Postcard, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0042)
  - Matisyahu - Exit-In, Nashville, TN 9/29/05, 2005 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0043)
  - Matisyahu - Flyers, press, old photos, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0044)
  - Matisyahu - Images, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0045)
  - Matisyahu - Israel photos, CD1, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0046)
  - Matisyahu - Israel photos, CD2, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0047)
  - Matisyahu - Live at Buffalo Billiards, SXSW, 2005 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0048)